

JORDAN SYER

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

PROFILE

I'm an aspiring Graphic Designer with a passion for brand identity and typography. Recently graduated with a BA (Hons) in Graphic Communication and 1 years' experience of working as the in-house Graphic Designer for a large Facilities Management company.

I am a self-motivated, hard working individual and I strive to achieve my very best and aim for a high standard in everything I do.

I have a passion for traditional looking styles that has led me to focus on clear and simple designs. I'm interested in taking inspiration from something old and developing it into something new and fresh. By simply using just a few colours and typefaces I like to create strong, memorable brand identities.

CONTACT



12 Rowan Drive, Dereham Norfolk NR20 3TY



www.jordansyer.co.uk



07767 394204



hello@jordansyer.co.uk

INTERESTS







EDUCATION

2012 - 2015 BATCHELORS DEGREE, GRAPHIC COMMUNICATION

NORWICH UNIVERSITY OF ARTS

2010 - 2012 **A LEVEL's**

DEREHAM SIXTH FORM COLLEGE

Graphic Design A*, Applied ICT B, Media Studies C

2006 - 2010 GCSE's

DEREHAM NEATHERD HIGH SCHOOL

English, English Literature, Mathematics, Science, Additional Science, French, Geography, Graphic Products, ICT, Religious Education



EXPERIENCE

2015 - 2016 **SERVEST UK**

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

- Working as the in-house Graphic Designer for a busy Marketing team and reporting to the Group Marketing Manager
- Designing a wide range of elements to promote the services our company offers and improve internal communications
- Creating various logos, e-shots, posters and print material as well as formatting and infographics for bids and tenders
- Working with Marketing Executives to ensure all work produced is to a high standard and in line with company standards and brand guidelines
- Regular liaison and communication with clients (up to Director level) to understand their requirements in order to create the design brief

2012 - 2015 MCDONALDS

CREW TRAINER

- Worked at McDonalds to support my time at University
- Promoted to Crew Trainer after completing the necessary development programme and was responsible for managing and training crew members for their day-to-day work and supporting the store management team

2012 - 2012 **OUCH CREATIVE**

PART TIME GRAPHIC DESIGNER

- Part time work with Ouch Creative, a design agency based in Dereham, Norfolk
- I created a number of different designs for one of the nightclubs they have as a client.
 My designs were commissioned by the nightclub and used as live promotional material



SKILLS & EXPERTISE

